Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 2)
  - New York City
    - Legal, General, 1942-1969 (Box 164, Folder 29)
    - Medical Society, 1962-1968 (Box 164, Folder 30)
    - Public Health, Correspondence, 1964-1974 (Box 164, Folder 31)
    - Public Health, Reports & General, 1952-1969 (Box 164, Folder 32)
    - "Attitudes & Practices of Private Physicians in the Area of Family to Medically Indigent Women," Gants & Scholl, New York City Department of Health, Health Research Training Program, Summer 1970 (Box 164, Folder 33)
    - "Delivery of Contraception Information and Services to Teenagers," Miller & Jones, New York City Department of Health, Health Research Training Program, Summer 1971 (Box 164, Folder 34)
    - Public Welfare, Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 164, Folder 35)
    - Public Welfare, General, 1953-1968 (Box 164, Folder 36)
    - Public Welfare, PP Special Affairs Program, 1964-1965 (Box 164, Folder 37)
    - Spanish Language Programs, 1963-1967 (Box 164, Folder 38)
    - Puerto Rican & Negro Groups, 1953-1963 (Box 164, Folder 39)
    - Spanish Speaking Program from 9/64, 1963-1966 (Box 164, Folder 40)
    - Spanish Speaking Program from M. Prentice 5/20/68, 1964-1967 (Box 164, Folder 41)
    - Sales Tax Exemption, 1955-1963 (Box 164, Folder 42)
    - Welfare Council, Re: Welfare Council PP Controversy, 1953 (Box 164, Folder 43)
    - Schools, General from 1965
      - 1964-1974 (Box 164, Folder 44)
      - 1975 (Box 164)
    - Fordham University, 1965-1969 (Box 164, Folder 45)
    - New School for Social Research, 1962-1969 (Box 164, Folder 46)
    - Yeshiva University, Albert Einstein College, 1964-1969 (Box 164, Folder 47)
    - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1960
      - 1960-1972 (Box 164, Folder 48)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 164)
    - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1965
      - 1965-1974 (Box 164, Folder 49)
      - 1975-1981 (Box 164)
    - PPNYC, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 164, Folder 50)
    - PPNYC, Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 164, Folder 51)
    - PP of NYC from 1970
      - 1970-1974 (Box 164, Folder 52)
      - 1975 (Box 164)
    - Planned Parenthood, 1966-1969 (Box 164, Folder 53)
    - PPNYC: Financial Arrangements from 1973
      - 1972-1974 (Box 164, Folder 54)
      - 1975 (Box 164)
    - PPNYC: Fund Raising Agreement, PPFA/PPNYC, 1979 (Box 164, Folder 55)
    - PPNYC, Fact Sheets: Abortion, Contraception, Sterilization, Request Forms, Spanish, English, Infertility, 1975-1976 (Box 164, Folder 56)
    - PPNYC: Hyde Amendment Injunction, Department Hew (Abortion, Medicaid), 1976 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - PPNYC: Loan Agreement, 1971-1972 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Merger, 1966 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - PPNYC: Proposals, 1968-1969 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, Minutes 1/8/74, 1974 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - PPNYC: Margaret Sanger Center, Training Program, Pamphlets, Publicity, Reports, General, Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - PPNYC: Public Issues and Action Committee, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Manhattan & Bronx, New York City PP, Reports, Clinics, 1958-1969 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - New York City PP, Reports, General, 1967-1971 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Manhattan & Bronx, New York City PP, Reports, General, 1965-1967 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Manhattan & Bronx, Reports, Members, 1963-1973 (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - PPNYC, Reports: Report to PPNYC on Labor & Industry Project, 1973-1974 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Manhattan & Bronx, New York City PP, Publicity, 1966-1974 (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - PPNYC: Title 1V-A, 1972-1973 (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - PPNYC: Abortion Education Program, 1973 (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Welfare, 1944-1964 (Box 165, Folder 16)
    - Welfare, 1964 (Box 165, Folder 17)
    - Public Health, 1944-1964 (Box 165, Folder 18)
    - Legislation, 1964-1965 (Box 165, Folder 19)
    - Legislation, 1965 (Box 165, Folder 20)
    - Hospitals, 1958-1965 (Box 165, Folder 21)
    - Newspaper Clips, 1963-1965 (Box 165, Folder 22)
  - New York State
    - Welfare, 1964-1968 (Box 165, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper Clips, 1963-1965 (Box 165, Folder 24)
    - Welfare, 1964-1965 (Box 165, Folder 25)
    - Welfare, Background, 1960-1964 (Box 165, Folder 26)
    - Welfare, Memos, Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 165, Folder 27)
    - Resolutions in Support of, circa 1960s (Box 165, Folder 28)
    - Hospitals, 1965 (Box 165, Folder 29)
    - Legislation, 1965 (Box 165, Folder 30)
    - New York City, Welfare, 1965 (Box 165, Folder 31)
    - Albany
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1953
        - 1953-1974 (Box 165, Folder 32)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 165)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1960
        - 1960-1974 (Box 165, Folder 33)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 165)
      - PP Albany & Rensselaer Counties, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 165, Folder 34)
      - PP Albany & Rensselaer City, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1978 (Box 165, Folder 35)
      - PP Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 165, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 165)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics, 1961-1964 (Box 165, Folder 37)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1955-1965 (Box 165, Folder 38)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1959-1970 (Box 165, Folder 39)
      - Field Trips, 1956-1965 (Box 165, Folder 40)
      - Publicity, 1955-1959 (Box 165, Folder 41)
    - Albion
      - Affiliation, PP Orleans County, 1968-1972 (Box 165, Folder 42)
      - PP, 1967-1969 (Box 165, Folder 43)
    - Auburn
      - PP, 1963-1965 (Box 165, Folder 44)
      - PP, Reports, General from 1964 (empty) (Box 165, Folder 45)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1965 (empty) (Box 165, Folder 46)
      - Publicity, 1964 (Box 165, Folder 47)
    - Babylon
      - Field Trips, 1956-1964 (Box 165, Folder 48)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1954-1971 (Box 165, Folder 49)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 165, Folder 50)
      - PP Center South Suffolk, Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 165, Folder 51)
      - PP South Suffolk, Reports, General, 1957-1963 (Box 165, Folder 52)
      - PP South Suffolk, Reports, Members, 1964-1968 (Box 165, Folder 53)
    - Batavia
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1974 (Box 166, Folder 1)
      - Affiliation, PP of Genesee County, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 166, Folder 2)
      - PP, 1967-1975 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Binghamton
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1953
        - 1953-1974 (Box 166, Folder 4)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 166)
      - Affiliation, PP Broome County, Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 166, Folder 5)
        - 1977-1981 (Box 166)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1964 (Box 166, Folder 6)
      - PP Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 166, Folder 7)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 166)
      - PP Broome County, Reports, General from 1959
        - 1959-1969 (Box 166, Folder 8)
        - 1975 (Box 166)
      - PP Broome County, Reports, Members, 1961-1972 (Box 166, Folder 9)
      - PP Broome County, Reports, Publicity, 1958-1963 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Bronxville, Affiliation - see Mt. Vernon, New York, 1949 (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1957-1962 (Box 166, Folder 12)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1955-1966 (Box 166, Folder 13)
      - PP Center, 1957-1966 (Box 166, Folder 14)
      - PP Center, Information, Mary Child Draper, First Chairman, 1972? (Box 166, Folder 15)
      - PP Committee of Brooklyn Board Manual, 1959 (Box 166, Folder 16)
      - Publicity, 1963-1966 (Box 166, Folder 17)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1964-1965 (Box 166, Folder 18)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1963-1965 (Box 166, Folder 19)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1962 (Box 166, Folder 20)
    - Buffalo
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1954
        - 1957-1974 (Box 166, Folder 21)
        - 1977-1979 (Box 166)
      - PP Center of Buffalo, New York, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 166, Folder 22)
      - PP of Buffalo, 1970
        - 1970-1973 (Box 166, Folder 23)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 166)
      - PP, 1964-1969 (Box 166, Folder 24)
      - Catholic Situation, 1956-1960 (Box 166, Folder 25)
      - PP Center, Reports, General, 1958-1966 (Box 166, Folder 26)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members, 1959-1972 (Box 166, Folder 27)
      - PP Correspondence
        - 1956-1974 (Box 166, Folder 28)
        - 1977-1981 (Box 166)
      - Dr. Guttmacher's Trips, 1962-1963 (Box 166, Folder 29)
      - PP Center, Publicity, 1958-1967 (Box 166, Folder 30)
      - Field Trips, Visits from 1954
        - 1954-1962 (Box 166, Folder 31)
        - 1978 (Box 166)
    - Cortland
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1972-1974 (Box 166, Folder 32)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 166, Folder 33)
        - 1975 (Box 166)
      - PP of Cortland County, 1971-1972 (Box 166, Folder 34)
    - Elmira
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1968
        - 1968-1972 (Box 166, Folder 35)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 166)
      - Affiliation, PP of the Southern Tier, Correspondence from 1968
        - 1968-1972 (Box 166, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 166)
      - PP from 1967
        - 1967-1973 (Box 166, Folder 37)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 166)
      - PP of Chemung County, Corning, Inc., Reports, General, 1968-1969 (Box 166, Folder 38)
      - PP of Chemung County, Corning, Inc., Reports, Members, 1969-1972 (Box 166, Folder 39)
    - Far Rockaway
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1949-1967 (Box 166, Folder 40)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence, 1949-1967 (Box 166, Folder 41)
      - PP Center South Shore, 1964-1969 (Box 166, Folder 42)
      - Merger: Far Rockaway, PP Center South Shore, 1969 (Box 166, Folder 43)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members, 1963-1967 (Box 166, Folder 44)
      - Field Trips, 1951-1964 (Box 166, Folder 45)
      - Publicity, 1958-1967 (Box 166, Folder 46)
    - Geneva (formerly Canandaigua)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents from 1969
        - 1969-1973 (Box 166, Folder 47)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 166)
      - Affiliation, PP of the Finger Lakes, Inc. (formerly Ontario County), Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 166, Folder 48)
      - Affiliation, PP of Ontario County, Correspondence from 1969
        - 1969-1973 (Box 166, Folder 49)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 166)
      - PP of the Finger Lakes, Inc. (formerly PP of Ontario County, Inc.) from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 166, Folder 50)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 166)
      - PP of Ontario County (formerly Canandaigua), Reports, Members, 1969-1970 (Box 166, Folder 51)
    - Glens Falls
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1967
        - 1967-1973 (Box 166, Folder 52)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 166)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1967
        - 1967-1973 (Box 166, Folder 53)
        - 1976-1981 (Box 166)
      - Southern Adirondack PP from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 166, Folder 54)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 166)
      - PP Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 166, Folder 55)
      - Reports, Members from 1966
        - 1966-1971 (Box 166, Folder 56)
        - 1979 (Box 166)
      - Southern Adirondack PP, Chapters, 1976 (Box 166, Folder 57)
      - Publicity, 1972 (Box 166, Folder 58)
    - Huntington
      - Affiliation, PP of Suffolk, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1979-1980 (Box 166, Folder 59)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws
        - 1950-1972 (Box 166, Folder 60)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 166)
      - Affiliation, PP of Suffolk, Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 166, Folder 61)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1950
        - 1950-1974 (Box 166, Folder 62)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 166)
      - Merger: Huntington PP, North Suffolk PP, Nassau County PP, East Suffolk, Patchogue, 1976-1978 (Box 166, Folder 63)
      - PP of North Suffolk, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 166, Folder 64)
      - PP of Suffolk, 1979 (Box 166, Folder 65)
      - PP Center North Suffolk from 1964
        - 1964-1971 (Box 166, Folder 66)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 166)
      - Field Trips, 1951-1962 (Box 166, Folder 67)
      - Reports, Clinics from 1967 (empty) (Box 166, Folder 68)
      - Reports, Members from 1962
        - 1962-1970 (Box 166, Folder 69)
        - 1976 (Box 166)
    - Ithaca
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1968
        - 1968-1972 (Box 166, Folder 70)
        - 1978 (Box 166)
      - Affiliation, PP of Tompkins County, Correspondence from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 166, Folder 71)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 166)
      - PP from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 166, Folder 72)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 166)
      - Proposed Agreement between Cornell University & PP of Tompkins County, 1970 (Box 166, Folder 73)
      - PP of Tompkins County, Reports, General, 1968-1971 (Box 166, Folder 74)
      - PP of Tompkins County, Reports, Members, 1968-1972 (Box 166, Folder 75)
    - Jamaica
      - Affiliation, PP Queens, Correspondence, 1958-1963 (Box 166, Folder 76)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1956-1965 (Box 166, Folder 77)
      - PP Committee Queens, 1964-1966 (Box 166, Folder 78)
      - PP Committee Queens, Reports, Members, 1962-1965 (Box 166, Folder 79)
      - Field Trips, 1951-1964 (Box 166, Folder 80)
    - Jamestown, PP, 1950 (Box 166, Folder 81)
    - Kingston
      - Affiliation, Ulster County, Maternal Health Center, 1953-1964 (Box 166, Folder 82)
      - Ulster County, Maternal Health Center from 1958
        - 1955-1964 (Box 166, Folder 83)
        - 1975 (Box 166)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1964 (Box 166, Folder 84)
      - Reports, 1955-1962 (Box 166, Folder 85)
    - Mineola (formerly East Meadow)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1978 (Box 166, Folder 86)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1978 (Box 166, Folder 87)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws
        - 1956-1972 (Box 166, Folder 88)
        - 1975 (Box 166)
      - Affiliation, PP Nassau County (formerly Mineola), Correspondence from 1962
        - 1962-1972 (Box 166, Folder 89)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 166)
      - PP Nassau County (formerly Mineola) from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 166, Folder 90)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 166)
      - PP Nassau County, 1978 (Box 166, Folder 91)
      - PP of Nassau County, 1962-1971 (Box 166, Folder 92)
      - Field Trips, 1951-1962 (Box 166, Folder 93)
      - Essay Contests, 1957-1958 (Box 166, Folder 94)
      - Reports, Clinics from 1967 (empty) (Box 166, Folder 95)
      - PP Nassau County, Reports, Members, 1958-1975 (Box 166, Folder 96)
      - Publicity, 1965-1969 (Box 166, Folder 97)
    - Mt. Kisco
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1953-1970 (Box 167, Folder 1)
      - Affiliation, Northern Westchester, Correspondence, 1961-1970 (Box 167, Folder 2)
      - PP of Northern Westchester, 1964-1972 (Box 167, Folder 3)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1964 (Box 167, Folder 4)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics, 1957-1965 (Box 167, Folder 5)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1962-1971 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Mt. Vernon
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1953-1967 (Box 167, Folder 7)
      - Affiliation, PP Southern Westchester, Correspondence, 1961-1970 (Box 167, Folder 8)
      - PP of Southern Westchester, 1958-1968 (Box 167, Folder 9)
      - Field Trips, 1959-1964 (Box 167, Folder 10)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1961-1964 (Box 167, Folder 11)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1959-1971 (Box 167, Folder 12)
      - PP, Publicity, 1954-1965 (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Newburgh
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1953
        - 1953-1974 (Box 167, Folder 14)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 167)
      - Affiliation, PP Orange County, Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 167, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 167)
      - PP Center Orange County from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 167, Folder 16)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 167)
      - Field Trips, 1953-1964 (Box 167, Folder 17)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1963-1970 (Box 167, Folder 18)
        - 1976 (Box 167)
      - Publicity, 1954-1957 (Box 167, Folder 19)
    - New Rochelle
      - Field Trips, 1951-1952 (Box 167, Folder 20)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Audits & Correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box 167, Folder 21)
      - PP Association, 1953-1958 (Box 167, Folder 22)
      - Reports, Members, 1954-1957 (Box 167, Folder 23)
    - Niagara Falls
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1960
        - 1950-1968 (Box 167, Folder 24)
        - 1976 (Box 167)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1973 (Box 167, Folder 25)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 167)
      - PP of Niagara County, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 167, Folder 26)
      - PP Association from 1964
        - 1965-1973 (Box 167, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 167)
      - Field Trips, 1956-1965 (Box 167, Folder 28)
      - Reports, Clinics from 1967 (empty) (Box 167, Folder 29)
    - Oneonta
      - Affiliation, Audits, Bylaws, Budgets from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 167, Folder 30)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 167)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 167, Folder 31)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 167)
      - PP Association of Delaware & Otsego Counties from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 167, Folder 32)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 167)
      - Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1973 (Box 167, Folder 33)
        - 1975 (Box 167)
    - Patchogue
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1964
        - 1964-1972 (Box 167, Folder 34)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 167)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 167, Folder 35)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 167)
      - PP of East Suffolk, Inc., Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 167, Folder 36)
      - PP Committee from 1964
        - 1963-1973 (Box 167, Folder 37)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 167)
      - Field Trips, 1964 (Box 167, Folder 38)
      - Reports, General, 1963-1969 (Box 167, Folder 39)
      - Reports, Members, 1964-1969 (Box 167, Folder 40)
    - Plattsburgh
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 167, Folder 41)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 167)
      - Affiliation, PP of Clinton County, Correspondence from 1972
        - 1971-1974 (Box 167, Folder 42)
        - 1975-1981 (Box 167)
      - PP of Clinton County from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 167, Folder 43)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 167)
    - Port Chester
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1951-1968 (Box 167, Folder 44)
      - Affiliation, PP Westchester County, Correspondence, 1959-1971 (Box 167, Folder 45)
      - PP Westchester County (Merger), 1964-1972 (Box 167, Folder 46)
      - PP Westchester County, Re: Merger, 1960-1969 (Box 167, Folder 47)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1965 (Box 167, Folder 48)
      - PP Eastern Westchester, Reports, Members, 1959-1970 (Box 167, Folder 49)
      - PP Eastern Westchester, Reports, General, 1960-1965 (Box 167, Folder 50)
    - Poughkeepsie
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1948
        - 1949-1973 (Box 167, Folder 51)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 167)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1950
        - 1950-1973 (Box 167, Folder 52)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 167)
      - PP of Dutchess, Ulster, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 167, Folder 53)
      - PP from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 167, Folder 54)
        - 1975 (Box 167)
      - PP League of Dutchess County, Branches, 1975 (Box 167, Folder 55)
      - Field Trips, 1956-1965 (Box 167, Folder 56)
      - PP Dutchess County, Reports, General, 1959-1965 (Box 167, Folder 57)
      - PP Dutchess County, Reports, Members, 1964-1972 (Box 167, Folder 58)
      - PP Dutchess County, Publicity, 1964-1965 (Box 167, Folder 59)
    - Rochester
      - Affiliation, PP League, Correspondence from 1961
        - 1964-1973 (Box 167, Folder 60)
        - 1976-1981 (Box 167)
      - PP Rochester & Monroe County, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 167, Folder 61)
      - PP League of Rochester & Monroe Counties, 1970-1979 (Box 167, Folder 62)
      - PP League, 1965-1969 (Box 167, Folder 63)
      - PP League, 1964-1965 (Box 167, Folder 64)
      - Field Trips, 1960-1964 (Box 167, Folder 65)
      - PP League, Reports, Clinics, 1958-1961 (Box 167, Folder 66)
      - PP League, Publicity, 1959-1965 (Box 167, Folder 67)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1948
        - 1948-1973 (Box 167, Folder 68)
        - 1976 (Box 167)
      - PP League, Reports, General, 1960-1965 (Box 167, Folder 69)
      - PP League, Reports, Members, 1963-1972 (Box 167, Folder 70)
    - Schenectady
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1960
        - 1960-1974 (Box 167, Folder 71)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 167)
      - PP from 1964
        - 1963-1974 (Box 167, Folder 72)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 167)
      - Audits, Budgets, Bylaws
        - 1949-1972 (Box 167, Folder 73)
        - 1978 (Box 167)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1965 (Box 168, Folder 1)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1961-1966 (Box 168, Folder 2)
      - PP League, Reports, Members, 1964-1971 (Box 168, Folder 3)
      - PP League, Publicity from 1964 1963-1976 (Box 168, Folder 4)
      - Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, 11/25/62, 1962-1964 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Staten Island, PP Committee of Staten Island, Closed in 1955, 1948-1962 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Syracuse
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1949-1973 (Box 168, Folder 7)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 168)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1950
        - 1950-1974 (Box 168, Folder 8)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 168)
      - Field Trips, 1960-1964 (Box 168, Folder 9)
      - PP Center
        - 1968-1974 (Box 168, Folder 10)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 168)
      - PP, 1964-1967 (Box 168, Folder 11)
      - Catholic Situation, 1959 (Box 168, Folder 12)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics, 1959-1960 (Box 168, Folder 13)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1972 (Box 168, Folder 14)
        - 1978 (Box 168)
      - PP, Publicity, 1965-1980 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Utica
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1965
        - 1965-1973 (Box 168, Folder 16)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 168)
      - Affiliation, PP of the Mohawk Valley, Correspondence from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 168, Folder 17)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 168)
      - PP of the Mohawk Valley, Inc. from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 168, Folder 18)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 168)
      - Family Planning of Mohawk Valley, 1965-1973 (Box 168, Folder 19)
      - PP Association of the Mohawk Valley, Chapters, 1976-1978 (Box 168, Folder 20)
      - PP Association Mohawk Valley, Workshop 1/13-14/1972 (Box 168, Folder 21)
      - PP Mohawk Valley, Clinic Handbook, 1973 (Box 168, Folder 22)
      - PP of the Mohawk Valley, Reports, Members, 1965-1972 (Box 168, Folder 23)
      - PP of the Mohawk Valley, Reports, General, 1965-1976 (Box 168, Folder 24)
      - Field Trips, 1965 (Box 168, Folder 25)
    - Watertown
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 168, Folder 26)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 168)
      - Affiliation, PP of Northern New York, Correspondence from 1966
        - 1966-1980 (Box 168, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 168)
      - PP of Northern New York from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 168, Folder 28)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 168)
      - PP of Northern New York, Institute on Human Sexuality & Birth for Mentally Retarded 9/21-22/1972 (Box 168, Folder 29)
      - PP of Northern New York, Reports, General, 1966-1968 (Box 168, Folder 30)
      - PP of Northern New York, Reports, Members from 1966
        - 1966-1972 (Box 168, Folder 31)
        - 1975 (Box 168)
    - West Nyack
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1968
        - 1969-1974 (Box 168, Folder 32)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 168)